A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office: Regulations of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1994
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Policy Office: Regulations of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1994
The Library of Virginia
35539
18.2 cu. ft. (52 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder on 31 October 1996.
Biographical Information
Lawrence Douglas Wilder was born in Richmond, Va., on January 17, 1931. He graduated from Virginia Union University in 1951 and afterwards was drafted into the Army, where he served in the Korean War from 1952-1953 and received a bronze star. He then attended the Howard University School of Law and graduated in 1959. Douglas Wilder was elected to the Virginia Senate in 1969 as the first African American member since Reconstruction and served in the Senate for five terms. In 1985, he was elected to the office of Lieutenant Governor as the first African American to be elected to statewide office in Virginia. L. Douglas Wilder won the election for Governor of Virginia in 1989 and served from January 13, 1990 to January 14, 1994. He was the first African American to be elected as Governor in United States.
During the Wilder Administration, the Policy Office was headed by Walter McFarlane, Executive Assistant for Policy, and four Special Assistants: Richard Taylor (Health and Human Resources, and Education), Robert Blue (Finance and Natural Resources), Jeff Nuechterlein (Economic Development and Transportation), and Lynne Porfiri (Administration and Public Safety). The Policy Office was responsible for review and coordination of all policy matters, including: review of proposed legislation from agencies and Cabinet; formulation of the Governor's legislative initiatives; tracking legislation and serving as legislative liaison; review of General Assembly approved legislation submitted to the Governor for signature, amendment or veto; review of death penalty clemency requests, as well as other pardon and restoration of rights requests; review of legal settlements and other legal matters from the Office of the Attorney General's Office; review of proposed regulations; review of all matters pertaining to the judiciary and writs of habeas corpus; review of proposed executive orders; assistance with speech writing; serving as staff for Governor's special commissions; administrative support for Governor's Fellows program; serving as special interest liaison; acting as in-house counsel; and all correspondence with policy implications or pertaining to sensitive or controversial issues requiring legal overview.
Scope and Content
Regulations, 1990-1994 during the administration of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder. The series is arranged alphabetically by folder title into 52 boxes. Includes regulation review forms, memoranda, recommendations, and summary of regulations. Includes regulations from the Air Pollution Control Board, Alcohol and Beverage Control Authority, Department of Agriculture, Department of Aviation, Department of Corrections, Department of Criminal Justice Services, Department of Health Professions, Department of Educations, Department of Housing and Community Development, Department of Medical Assistance Services, Department of Mines, Minerals, and Energy, Department of Social Services, and Department of State Police.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Contents List
- ABC--Emergency Regulations--Credit Card Sales, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ABC--Emergency Regulations--Informal Conferences--VR 125-01-2 Sec. 1.22, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ABC--Emergency Regulations--Waiver of Banquet License Fee--VR 125-01-5, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ABC--Regulations, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ABC--VR 125-01-6, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ABC--VR 125-01-1, VR 125-01-2, VR 125-01-3, VR 125-01-5, VR 125-01-6, VR 125-01-7 (1 of 2), 1991-1992. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ABC--VR 125-01-1, VR 125-01-2, VR 125-01-3, VR 125-01-5, VR 125-01-6, VR 125-01-7 (2 of 2), 1991-1992. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ABC--VR 125-01-2, VR 125-01-3, VR 125-01-4, VR 125-01-5, VR 125-01-6 (1 of 2), 1991-1992. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ABC--VR 125-01-2, VR 125-01-3, VR 125-01-4, VR 125-01-5, VR 125-01-6 (2 of 2), 1991-1992. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ABC--VR 125-01-2, VR 125-01-3, VR 125-01-4, VR 125-01-5, VR 125-01-7, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ABC--VR 125-01-2, VR 125-01-3, VR 125-01-4, VR 125-01-5, VR 125-01-7, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Agriculture--Admission of Livestock, Poultry, Companion Animals, and Birds into Virginia--VR 115-02-12, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Agriculture--Emergency Regulations Governing the Sale and use of Granular Formations of Carbofuran--VR 115-04-24, 1991-1992. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Agriculture--Emergency Regulations on Oxygenated Gasoline--VR115-04-8, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Agriculture--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Agriculture--Enforcement of the Virginia Gasoline and Motor Fuels Law--VR 115-04-12, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Agriculture--Enforcement of Virginia Pesticides Law--VR 115-04-03 (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Agriculture--Enforcement of Virginia Pesticides Law--VR 115-04-03 (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Agriculture--Food for Human Consumption--VR 115-05-13, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Agriculture--Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (1 of 4), 1992-1993. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Agriculture--Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (2 of 4), 1992-1993. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Agriculture--Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (3 of 4), 1992-1993. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Agriculture--Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (4 of 4), 1992-1993. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Agriculture--Oxygenation of Gasoline--VR 115-04-28 (1 of 2), 1992-1993. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Agriculture--Oxygenation of Gasoline--VR 115-04-28 (2 of 2), 1992-1993. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Agriculture--Pesticide Applicator Certification--VR 115-04-23 (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Agriculture--Pesticide Applicator Certification--VR 115-04-23 (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Agriculture--Pesticide Control Enforcement of the Virginia Pesticide Law--VR 115-04-03, 1991. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Agriculture--Pesticide Control--Pesticide Applicator Certification--VR 115-04-23, 1991. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Agriculture--Prevention, Control, and Eradication of Brucellosis of Bovidae in Virginia--VR 115-02-03, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Agriculture--Prevention, Control, and Eradication of Tuberculosis in Bovidae, Cervidae, and Capridae in Virginia--VR 115-02-02, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Agriculture--Rules and Regulations Governing Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (1 of 6), 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Agriculture--Rules and Regulations Governing Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (2 of 6), 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Agriculture--Rules and Regulations Governing Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (3 of 6), 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Agriculture--Rules and Regulations Governing Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (4 of 6), 1991-1993. (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Agriculture--Rules and Regulations Governing Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (5 of 6), 1991-1993. (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Agriculture--Rules and Regulations Governing Grade "A" Milk--VR 115-05-01 (6 of 6), 1991-1993. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, W, 1991. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01 (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01 (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution (Revision U)--VR 120-01, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, BB, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, BB, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, CC, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, DD, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, DD, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, EE, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, U, 1992. (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, W, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control of Motor Vehicle Emissions--VR 120-99-03, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution--VR 120-01, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Air Pollution Control Board--Emergency Regulation Revision KK-E--Permit Program Fees, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Aviation--Licensing and Operation of Airports and Aircraft and Obstructions to Airspace, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Board--Public Participation Procedures--VR 173-01-00, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Commerce--Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, and Landscape Architecture--VR 130-01-02, 1991-1992. (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Commerce--Asbestos Licensing--VR 190-05-1:1, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Commerce--Board for Accountancy Regulations--VR 105-01-06, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Commerce--Board of Accountancy--Continuing Professional Education Sponsor Registration, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Commerce--Board of Commerce--Practice for Hearing Officers--VR 190-02-1, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Commerce--Board of Contractors--VR 220-01-3, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Commerce--Board for Cosmetology Nail Technicians, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Commerce--Board of Hearing Aid Specialists--VR 375-01-03, 1991-1992. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Commerce--Board of Opticians--VR 505-01-01, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Commerce--Board for Professional Soil Scientists Regulations--VR 627-02-02, 1992-1993. (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Commerce--Board for Waste Management Facility Operators--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 674-01-01, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Commerce--Emergency Regulations for Architects and Engineers, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Commerce--Emergency Regulations--Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Commerce--Emergency Regulations--Board of Accountancy, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Commerce--Emergency Regulations--Private Security Services Businesses, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Commerce--Emergency Regulations--Real Estate Board--Continuing Education Requirements, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Commerce--Employment Agency--VR 190-06-1, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Commerce--Private Security Services Businesses--VR 190-04-1:1, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Commerce--Real Estate Board--Emergency Regulations--Common Interest Associations Annual Reports, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Commerce--Real Estate Board--Emergency Regulations--Correspondence Courses for Pre-Licensing, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Commerce--Real Estate Board--Fair Housing, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Commerce--Real Estate Board Licensing--VR 585-01-1, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Commerce--Real Estate Appraisers Board--Licensure of Appraisers--VR 581-01-03, 1991-1992. (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Commerce--Real Estate Appraiser Board--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 583-01-04, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Commerce--Soil Scientists Board--Amend Fee Structure--VR 627-02-01, 1990-1991. (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Commerce--Waste Management Facility Operators--674-01-02, 1992-1993. (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Commerce--Waterworks and Wastewater Operators--VR 675-01-03, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Commerce--Waterworks and Wastewater Operators--VR 675-01-03, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Conservation and Recreation--Public Participation Guidelines, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Conservation and Recreation--Soil and Water Conservation--Public Participation Procedures, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Corrections--Certification Process--VR 230-02-003.1, 1992-1993. (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Corrections--Community Diversion Program Standards--VR 230-30-002, 1991. (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Corrections--Community Residential Programs--VR 230-30-004.1, 1992-1993. (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Corrections--Emergency Regulations--Planning, Design, Construction, and Reimbursement of Local Correctional Facilities, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Corrections--Emergency Regulations--Reimbursement of Local Corrections Facilities Construction Cost, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Corrections--Minimum Standards for Jail and Lockups--VR 230-30-01, 1990-1991. (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Corrections--Minimum Standards for Jails and Lockups--VR 230-30-01, 1992-1993. (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Corrections--Probation and Parole Standards--VR 230-30-003, 1990-1991. (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Corrections--State Reimbursement of Local Correctional Facility Construction Costs--VR 230-30-008, 1990-1991. (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Corrections--Supervision Fee--VR 230-30-007, 1990-1992. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Corrections--Work Study Release Standards for Local Facilities--VR 230-30-006, 1991-1992. (Box 13, Folder 4)
- DCJS [Department of Criminal Justice Services]--Certification of Criminal Justice Instructors--VR 240-01-02, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 5)
- DCJS--Certification of Criminal Justice Instructors--VR 240-01-12, 1991-1992. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- DCJS--Compulsory In-service Training Standards--VR 240-01-2, 1991-1992. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- DCJS--Compulsory Minimum Training Standards for Dispatchers--VR 240-01-5, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 8)
- DCJS--Compulsory Minimum Training Standards for Jailers, etc.--VR 240-01-4, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 9)
- DCJS--Compulsory Minimum Training Standards for Private Security Personnel--VR 240-03-1, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 10)
- DCJS--Court Appointed Special Advocate Program--VR 240-04-3, 1991-1992. (Box 13, Folder 11)
- DCJS--Criminal History Record Information Use and Security--VR 240-02-1, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 12)
- DCJS--Emergency Regulations--Forfeited Drug Asset Sharing Program, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 1)
- DCJS--Emergency Regulations--Private Security Services, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 2)
- DCJS--Forfeited Drug Asset Sharing Program--VR 240-04-2, 1991-1992. (Box 14, Folder 3)
- DCJS--McGruff House Program--VR 240-04-1,. (Box 14, Folder 4)
- DCJS--Regulations, 1990-1991. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Deaf and Hard of Hearing--Distribution of Telecommunication Equipment--VR 245-02-01, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Deaf and Hard of Hearing--Emergency Regulations--Distribution of Telecommunication Equipment--VR 245-02-01, 1991-1992. (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Deaf and Hard of Hearing--Emergency Regulations--Procedures for Distribution of Technological Assistive Devices, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Deaf and Hard of Hearing--Interpreter Services for the Deaf--VR 245-03-01, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 9)
- DHP [Department of Health Professions]--Board of Audiology and Speech-Language Pathology--VR 155-01-2:2, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 10)
- DHP--Board of Dentistry--Certification to Apply Schedule IV Topical Drugs--VR 255-01-1, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 11)
- DHP--Board of Dentistry--Emergency Regulations--VR 255-01-1, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 12)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Certification of Optometrists--VR 465-09-01, 1990-1991. (Box 14, Folder 13)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Certification of Radiological Technology Practitioners--VR465-10-10, 1991-1992. (Box 14, Folder 14)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Emergency Regulations--Fees for Licensure Renewal, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 15)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Optometrists to Prescribe for and Treat Certain Diseases--VR 465-09-01, 1991-1992. (Box 14, Folder 16)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Physical Therapy--VR 465-03-01, 1991-1992. (Box 15, Folder 1)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Physician's Assistant--VR 465-05-01, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 2)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Practice of Licensed Acupuncturists--VR 465-11-01, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 3)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Practice of Medicine, Osteopathy, Podiatry, Chiropractic, Clinical Psychology, and Acupuncture--VR 465-02-01, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 4)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Practice of Occupational Therapy--VR 465-08-01, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 5)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Practice of Physical Therapy,. (Box 15, Folder 6)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Practice of Physician's Assistant--VR 475-05-01, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 7)
- DHP--Board of Medicine--Respiratory Therapy Practitioners--VR 465-04-01, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 8)
- DHP--Boards of Medicine and Nursing--Prescriptive Authority for Nurse Practitioners--VR 465-12-1, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 9)
- DHP--Board of Nursing--VR 495-01-1, 1992-1993. (Box 15, Folder 10)
- DHP--Board of Nursing--APA Exempt Federal Law and Regulation Required--VR 495-01-1, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 11)
- DHP--Board of Nursing Home Administration--Increase Fees and Amend Mandatory Continuing Education Requirements, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 1)
- DHP--Board of Nursing Home Administrators--VR 500-01-2:1, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 2)
- DHP--Board of Optometry--Fee Changes and Clarifications--VR 510-01-1, 1991-1992. (Box 16, Folder 3)
- DHP--Board of Pharmacy--VR 530-01-02, 1991-1992. (Box 16, Folder 4)
- DHP--Board of Pharmacy--Implement 1992 Legislation--VR 530-01-1, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 5)
- DHP--Board of Pharmacy--Practice of Pharmacy--VR 530-01-1 (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 6)
- DHP--Board of Pharmacy--Practice of Pharmacy--VR 530-01-1 (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 7)
- DHP--Board of Pharmacy--Practice of Pharmacy--VR 530-01-1 (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 16, Folder 8)
- DHP--Board of Pharmacy--Practitioners of the Healing Arts to Sell Controlled Substances, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 1)
- DHP--Board of Professional Counselors--VR 560-01-02, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 2)
- DHP--Board of Psychology--Emergency Regulations--Fees Associated with Practice--VR 565-01-2, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 3)
- DHP--Board of Psychology--Practice of Psychology--VR 565-01-2 (1 of 4), 1992. (Box 17, Folder 4)
- DHP--Board of Psychology--Practice of Psychology--VR 565-01-2 (2 of 4), 1992. (Box 17, Folder 5)
- DHP--Board of Psychology--Practice of Psychology--VR 565-01-2 (3 of 4), 1992. (Box 17, Folder 6)
- DHP--Board of Psychology--Practice of Psychology--VR 565-01-2 (4 of 4), 1992. (Box 17, Folder 7)
- DHP--Board of Psychology--Practice of Psychology--VR 565-01-02, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 8)
- DHP--Board of Psychology--Practice of Psychology--VR 565-01-02, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 9)
- DHP--Board of Social Work--VR 620-01-2, 1990-1992. (Box 18, Folder 1)
- DHP--Funeral Directors and Embalmers--Funeral Services Trainee Program--VR 320-01-04, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 2)
- DHP--Funeral Directors and Embalmers--Preneed Funeral Contracts--VR 320-01-3, 1992. (Box 18, Folder 3)
- DHP--Funeral Directors and Embalmers--Regulations for Preneed Funeral Planning, 1992-1993. (Box 18, Folder 4)
- DHP--Funeral Directors and Embalmers--Resident Trainee Program for Funeral Service, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 5)
- DMAS [Department of Medical Assistance Services]--Amount, Duration, and Scope of Services: Fertility Services, Optional Drugs, Rebates, and Drug Dispensing Fees, 1992-1993. (Box 18, Folder 6)
- DMAS--Case Management for Elderly, 1991-1992. (Box 18, Folder 7)
- DMAS--Case Management for Mental Retardation Waiver Clients, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 8)
- DMAS--Client Appeals--VR 460-04-8.7, 1993. (Box 18, Folder 9)
- DMAS--Client Medical Management Program--VR 460-04-8.3, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 10)
- DMAS--Community Mental Health--Mental Retardation Services, 1992. (Box 19, Folder 1)
- DMAS--Confidentiality and Disclosure of Information Concerning Medicaid Applicants and Recipients, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 2)
- DMAS--Cost Management Initiative for PIRS and Amount, Duration, and Scope of Services, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 3)
- DMAS--DMHMRSAS--Community and Waiver Services, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 4)
- DMAS--Drug Utilization Review in Nursing Facilities--VR 460-05-3000, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 5)
- DMAS--Drug Utilization Review--VR 460-04-4.2600, 1992-1993. (Box 19, Folder 6)
- DMAS--Elimination of Nursing Home Bed Hold Days, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 7)
- DMAS--Enrollment of Psychologists Clinical, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 8)
- DMAS--Establishing Payment Rate--Inpatient Hospital Care--Disproportionate Share Adjustment for State Teaching Hospitals, 1992. (Box 19, Folder 9)
- DMAS--EPSDT and Inpatient Psychiatric Services, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 10)
- DMAS--Fee-for-Services Reimbursement for Home Health Services, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 11)
- DMAS--Fee-for-Services Reimbursement for Home Health Services (1 of 2), 1992. (Box 20, Folder 1)
- DMAS--Fee-for-Services Reimbursement for Home Health Services (2 of 2), 1992. (Box 20, Folder 2)
- DMAS--Health Insurance Premium Payment Program, 1992-1993. (Box 20, Folder 3)
- DMAS--Home Community Based Services for Persons with Mental Retardation--VR 460-04-8.12, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
- DMAS--Home Health Services, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 5)
- DMAS--Income Scales for Indigent Children, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 6)
- DMAS--Inpatient Hospital Care--Inpatient Outlier Adjustment, 1992. (Box 20, Folder 7)
- DMAS--Inpatient Hospital Settlement Agreement, 1992. (Box 20, Folder 8)
- DMAS--Limitation of XIX payment of XVIII Part B Coinsurance, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 9)
- DMAS--Maximum Obstetric and Pediatric Payments, 1992. (Box 20, Folder 10)
- DMAS--MEDALLION--VR 460-04-8.14, 1992-1993. (Box 20, Folder 11)
- DMAS--Nursing Facility Reimbursement System--PIRS--VR 460-03-4.1940:1, 1991-1992. (Box 20, Folder 12)
- DMAS--Nursing Facility Resident Review Requirements (Final)--Exempt from APA, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 13)
- DMAS--Nursing Home Payment System, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 14)
- DMAS--Omnibus Technical Amendment, 1991-1993. (Box 21, Folder 1)
- DMAS--Outpatient Rehabilitative Services, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
- DMAS--Outpatient Rehab Services Copay: Remove XVIII Cap on Fees, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 3)
- DMAS--Outstationing Eligibility Workers, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 4)
- DMAS--Reduction of Threshold Days for Hospital Utilization Review--SSOP, 1991-1992. (Box 21, Folder 5)
- DMAS--Reimbursement Adjustment for Non-Emergency Care in Emergency Rooms, 1992. (Box 21, Folder 6)
- DMAS--Restoration of Income and Resource Methodologies, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 7)
- DMAS--Specialized Care Services Reimbursement, 1992. (Box 21, Folder 8)
- DMAS--State Provider Disputes and Date of Acquisition, 1992. (Box 21, Folder 9)
- DMAS--Transportation Program, 1992. (Box 21, Folder 10)
- DMV--Commercial Driver Training Schools--VR 485-10-9001, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 11)
- DMV--Commercial Driver Training School--VR 485-60-9201, 1991-1992. (Box 21, Folder 12)
- DMV--Permit Registration of Vehicles with Proof of Tax Payment--VR 485-60-8401, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 13)
- DMV--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 485-10-8401, 1991-1992. (Box 21, Folder 14)
- DMV--Public Participation Guidelines--Emergency Regulations, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 15)
- DMV--Salvage Act--VR 485-60-9202, 1992. (Box 21, Folder 16)
- DPOR [Department of Professional and Occupational Regulations]--Asbestos Contractor and Workers Public Participation Guidelines--VR 190-00-01:1, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 1)
- DPOR--Board for Auctioneers--Public Participation Guidelines--VR150-01-1:2, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 2)
- DPOR--Board for Geology--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 335-01-1:1, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 3)
- DPOR--Board for Opticians--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 505-01-1:2, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 4)
- DPOR--Board for Professional Soil Scientists--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 627-01-1:1, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 5)
- DPOR--Polygraph Examiners Advisory Board--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 190-00-03:1, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 6)